iOS Developer OHN LIMA

thejohnlima@icloud.com

.

https://linkedin.com/in/thejohnlima

O

thejohnlima

EXPERIENCE

PagSeguro UOL

iOS Developer | July 2018 - March 2021

+1

(646)

Working with native applications using Swift

Stormbreaker Studios

Freelancer iOS Developer | January 2020 - December 2020

Working in iOS applications using Swift

BRQ

iOS Developer | April 2017 - June 2018

Working with native applications using Swift and Objective-C

Magna Sistemas

iOS Developer | February 2016 - April 2017

Working with native applications using Swift...

Urban Summer

iOS Developer | March 2015 - February 2016

Working with native and hybrid mobile Apps...

EDUCATION

Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

System Analysis and Development | February 2014 - June 2018

Learning a lot of concepts about iOS development in Impacta, Sao Paulo, Brazil

iOS Developer | March 2013 - December 2014

SKILLS

About me

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept ofthe ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.